

# MD Jahid Bin Amin

#### CONTACT INFO

+880 1954598198

md.jahid.bin.amin@gmail.com

Motijheel Dhaka, Bangladesh

#### **LANGUAGES**

BANGLA ENGLISH

URDU



## **HOBBIES**





**SPORTS** 



MUSIC

TRAVEL



# **ABOUT ME**

Currently in my third year of studying BSC at BRAC University. I have excellent communication skills, enabling me to ef ectively communicate with a wide range of people. I am seeing a position in the industry in which I can put into practice my knowledge and experience, ultimately benef ting the operations of the organisation that I work for.



# **EXPERIENCE**

 BRAC University Adventure Club

> Senior Executive 2019 - Current

 BRAC University Computer Club

> Senior Executive 2019 - Current

 Graphic Desginer at Course Platoon

As an Intern

BRAC University Adventure Club was established with an aim to provide a platform that gives the f avor of proper adventure to the students of BRAC University.

BRAC University Computer Club (BUCC) is the oldest club of BRAC university founded by Mr. Annajiat Alim Rasel in 2001.

Course Platoon is a platform that stands as a unique provider of modern skill sets to ensure the employment of potential youths in Bangladesh.



# **EDUCATION**

BRAC University

2019 - 2023

Govt. Science College

2016 - 2018

## **DEGREE**

Bachelor in Computer Science & Engineering

## **DEGREE**

Higher Secondary School Certif cate (2016-2018)



LEVEL

Adobe Illustrator,Photoshop,Premiere Pro

 Java, Python, CSS, Word-press

Fluent in English speaking,
Communication

INTERMEDIATE ★★

INTERMEDIATE \* \* \* \*